本字幕由YYeTs字幕組原創翻譯
www.ZiMuZu.tv 歡迎交流
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    ustvboom
了解最新影視字幕發布信息
饑餓
的青春
第二季  第三集
我好沮喪啊
I am so depressed.
再也不想去農貿市場了
I never want to go to the farmer's market again.
我們配不上這甘藍
We don't even deserve this kale.
我想甘藍[殺]了自己
I wanna kale myself.
我們為什么非得撞見莉澤特
Why did we have to run into Lizette?
-莉澤特  -莉澤特
- Lizette. - Lizette?
高中的薄唇莉澤特  怎么就
How does "Thin-lipped" Lizette from high school
有了唇膏帝國啊
have a lip-balm empire?
記得大家以前叫她蜥蜴嘴嗎
Remember when people used to call her "Lizard lips"?
是啊  我們真刻薄
Yeah. Wow, we were so mean.
她那么忙
Yeah, for someone so busy,
居然還有空吹噓自己
she certainly had plenty of time to brag about herself.
難以置信我們23歲時就已經失敗了
I can't believe we're 23 and already washed up.
是吧  我們的夢想怎么了
Right? What happened to our dreams?
你要成為下一個茱莉亞·蔡爾德
You were gonna be the next Julia Child
開著自己的餐廳  寫了烹飪書  還有電視節目
with your own restaurant and cookbook and TV show.
你本來要擁有帝國的
You were gonna have an empire.
我沒有
Yeah, I don't have that.
我也沒在華爾街有間辦公室
And I don't have a corner office on Wall Street
還有個暗戀我的英俊助理
with a hot assistant who's secretly in love with me.
-這是個警鐘  -是啊
- This is a wake-up call. - Yes it is.
-我們得開始建立關系網了  -是啊
- We got to start networking. - Yes we do.
我們得給我們認識的
We've got to start emailing
所有成功人士發郵件
all the successful people we know
來幫我們更上一層樓
to help us get to the next level.
我現在就去
Yes, I'm doing that right now.
好
Okay.
我不認識什么成功人士
Wow, I don't know any successful people.
你記得洛根·勞林斯嗎
Ooh, do you remember Logan Rawlings?
那個拉拉雜志編輯
The lesbian magazine editor
-你跟她假約會來幫助喬什  -是的
- you fake-dated to help Josh. - Yeah!
她很成功
She's totally successful
能幫我更上一層樓
and could totally help me get to the next level.
上一層樓是什么
What is the next level?
你記得你讀過的那些美食文章嗎
You know all those food articles you read about?
你說  我也可以寫得出
You're like, "I could've written that,"
但你什么也沒寫
but you never write anything?
是啊  我很擅長
Yeah, I'm really good at that.
不如你為她的雜志寫一篇美食文章吧
Well, why don't you write a food article for her magazine?
好主意  索菲亞
That is a great idea, Sofia.
你是我認識的最聰明的廢柴
You are the smartest loser I know.
早上好  各位
Morning, guys.
最近怎么樣
How's it going, buddy?
你沒事吧  需要擁抱嗎
Are you okay? Do you need a hug?
我知道這幾周很難熬
Look, I know it's been a rough few weeks
我取消了婚禮
with my wedding being called off
加比又跟庫珀和好  但我翻篇了
and Gabi getting back with Cooper, but I'm over it.
我沒事了
I'm fine.
當然啦
Sure you are.
-真勇敢  -是啊
- Such a trooper. - Yeah.
翻譯  冰藍  胖兔純   aaaBao
少來了  我說真的
Hey, stop it. I'm serious.
校對  冰藍
我朝前看了
I've moved on.
如果你們想要薪水  你們也要這樣
If you guys want your paychecks, you will too.
時間軸  aaaBao
瞧瞧你身材有多好
Wow, look how fit you are.
后期  斯人   總監  總監和小姨子跑了
一定是因為你朝前看了
Must be all that moving on you're doing.
各位  猜猜怎么
Hey, guys, guess what?
你要搬去中國了  真難過  拜拜
You're moving to China. So sad. Bye!
不是
No.
我決定讓我的事業更上一層樓
I decided I needed to take my career to the next level,
所以我打給了洛根·勞林斯
So I called Logan Rawlings--
記得嗎  艾略特撮合了我和那個拉拉
Remember? The lesbian that Elliot pimped me out to?
真好笑
That was funny.
她給我回電話了  想聽聽我寫的
Well, she called me back and she wants to hear my ideas
美食文章的主意
on a food article written by me.
加比  太棒了  我沒有任何感覺
Gabi, that's great. I feel nothing...
除了開心
but happiness...
為你開心
for you.
是庫珀
Oh, that's Cooper.
親愛的  我有最好的新聞
Hi, sweetcakes. I have the best news.
瞧  她在跟庫珀聊天
See? She's talking to Cooper
我沒事
and I'm fine.
不  我的新聞不是想你了
No, my news isn't that I miss you.
那可不是新聞  我一直都想你啊
That wouldn't be news. I miss you all the time,
我的超級庫珀熊
my super Cooper bear.
瞧  我...
See, I'm--
不好  我去辦公室了
Not fine. I will be in my office
戴上降噪耳機
with my noise-canceling headphones.
我的工資單搞錯了
My check's wrong.
喬什多付了我錢
Josh overpaid me.
多付了很多
Like way overpaid me.
他少付了很多錢給我
Well, he way underpaid me.
等等
Oh wait.
這是你的支票
This is your check.
你賺的錢比我多嗎
You make more money than me?
你是他管家  我可是他的公關
You're his housekeeper. I'm his publicist!
那又如何  我跟喬什很久了
So? I've been with Josh for a long time.
是啊
Exactly.
他不該意識到你有多沒價值嗎
Shouldn't he realize how worthless you are?
少來了
Oh, stop it.
你只用進去要求漲工資
All you got to do is walk in there and ask for a raise.
我每隔一個月都去
I do it every other month.
我不能去
I could never do that.
為什么
Why not?
我知道我表現得
Look, I know I come off
是個自信的文藝復興人
as this confident self-assured renaissance man...
對誰啊
To who?
但我小時候
But, when I was a kid,
我就有一次要求多給點零花錢
the one time I asked for a bigger allowance,
我爸就瘋了
my dad went crazy.
我18歲之前每周都只有50美分
I made 50 cents a week till I was 18.
等我攢夠威猛樂隊演唱會的門票時
By the time I saved up enough money to go to a Wham! Concert,
他們解散了
they broke up!
加比·戴蒙德小姐
Miss Gabi Diamond.
洛根  非常感謝你來見我
Hey, Logan, thank you so much for seeing me.
當我告訴朋友們  我跟偉大的
When I told my friends that I had a meeting
-洛根·勞林斯有約時  -別
- with the great Logan Rawlings-- - Don't.
別那樣做
Don't do that.
別做什么
Don't do what?
拍我馬屁
Kiss my ass.
不不  我不會的  我是說我不能
No, no, no, I wouldn't. I mean, I couldn't.
我是說  你該說話了
I mean-- you should talk now.
我想要對舊金山食物界
I want a totally unique and hip
獨特而時尚的觀點
take on the San Francisco food scene
之前沒人有過
that hasn't been done before.
我有很多很酷的主意
Well, I have a ton of cool ideas.
我有兩分鐘時間
And I have two minutes.
你中風了嗎  快說
Are you stroking out? Go.
好吧  你知道最近大家都在吃椒鹽卷餅吧
Okay, well, you know how everybody these days is eating pretzels?
不知道
No.
就是這樣  我想的是
Well, they are. I was thinking
《椒鹽卷餅的30個新花樣》
"30 new twists on pretzels."
懂嗎  椒鹽卷餅  花樣[轉折]
Get it? Pretzel? Twist.
我有個轉折  我一點也不喜歡
Here's a twist. I love it 0%.
好吧  我還有很多別的主意
Okay, well, I have a ton of other ideas.
怎樣用三明治震驚四座
"How to impress with a panini."
懂嗎  三明治  震驚四座
Get it? Panini? Impress?
你知道我要發表[按]什么嗎
You know what I'm gonna press?
這個按鈕  拉斐爾  送戴蒙德小姐出去
This button. Rafael, please show Miss Diamond out.
不不  聽著  洛根
No, no, no, listen, Logan.
我是個很棒的大廚
I am a great chef.
我可以坐在這里
I could sit here and toss out
說出一堆可以寫的很棒的食物
a bunch of great foods to write about,
-但我不會那樣做  -還有30秒
- but I'm not gonna do that. - 30 seconds.
培根生菜番茄三明治  焗烤意粉
Blt's, tetrazzini,
名貴奶酪  奶油杏仁糖  煎餅  千層面
fancy cheeses, nougat, hotcakes, lasagna--
-你剛說了大麻蛋糕嗎  -沒有
- Wait, did you just say... pot cakes? - No.
也許吧
Maybe.
-這主意很棒  -所以我才說
- That's a fantastic idea. - Which is why I said it.
大麻食物現在很流行
Pot edibles are so hot right now.
是啊
Yeah. Yeah they are.
大家都在說它
Everybody's talking about it,
然后忘記了自己在說什么
then forgetting what they're talking about.
不幸的是  這毀掉了食物的味道
Unfortunately, it ruins the way food tastes.
很難烹飪
It's hard to cook with.
相信我  沒人在我的食物中嘗到過大麻的味道
Trust me, no one has ever tasted pot in any of my food.
好吧  兩天內給我
Okay, get me a killer 500-word piece
一篇用大麻烹飪的500字文章
about cooking with pot in two days
我在本月的雜志上發布
and I'll run it in this month's issue.
拜托  兩天  我一天就能給你寫好
Please, two days? I could have it for you in one.
-真的嗎  -不  我需要兩天時間
- Really? - No, I'm gonna need two.
說成功不會在一夜之間發生的人
Whoever said success doesn't happen overnight
肯定沒跟我過過夜
has never spent the night with me.
洛根想要我給她的雜志寫篇文章
Logan wants me to write an article for her magazine.
天啊  我要跟經理合伙人開會
Oh my god. I got a meeting with one of the managing partners
談談我的升職問題
to talk about a promotion.
好棒  我們買一大袋大麻來慶祝吧
That's amazing. Let's celebrate by buying a big bag of marijuana.
你說啥
Uh, what?
我的文章內容是關于烹飪大麻的
My article's about cooking with pot.
-大麻  -沒錯
- Pot? - Yeah.
加比  說真的  你從沒做過大麻食物
Gabi. Seriously, you've never cooked with pot.
的確  我也不知道怎么用襪子粉刷
Yeah, I didn't know how to paint with socks either,
可我們的廁所刷得不錯啊
but our bathroom turned out great.
知道嗎  你說得對  看看我們
You know what? You're right. Look at us.
我們自我鞭策  世界的大門就對我們敞開了
We push ourselves and the world opens up.
說到毒販子[推手]
Speaking of pushers,
"十元"戴夫還住在樓下嗎
does dime-bag Dave still live downstairs?
他搬走了  搬去監獄住了
No, he moved. To jail.
要是你想做這道菜  至少別走歪路
If you're gonna do it, at least do it honestly.
裝病去搞一張藥用大麻卡
Fake an illness and get a cannabis card
我奶奶就是這么做的
like my nana did.
不知道行不行  我只會在認識的人面前撒謊
I don't know. I'm only good at lying to people I know.
這事讓我開始感到有點緊張焦慮了
I'm starting to get nervous and anxious about this.
太好了  我們只要跟醫生說
That's perfect. Just tell the doctor
你需要大麻來緩解緊張情緒
you need weed to calm your nerves.
真是個好主意
Hey, that's a great idea.
那我就不用撒謊了
Then I won't be lying.
但我不撒謊的話就不會緊張
But since I won't be lying, I won't be nervous.
所以我得撒謊
So I will be lying.
但同時又不撒謊
But I also won't be.
你已經嗑嗨了嗎
Are you stoned already?
-你確定這招管用嗎  -讓我去跟醫生說
- Are you sure this is gonna work? - Let me do the talking.
我知道該怎么做  姐是街頭混大的
I know what I'm doing. I'm from the streets.
你是在有警衛的高檔社區長大的
You grew up in a gated community.
是的  但那沒攔住外人
Yeah, but was it keeping people out
也沒關住我們  小妞
or us in, chica?
得了吧  索菲亞
Come on, Sofia.
永遠別說真名
Never say your real name.
叫我小索
Call me Lil So-So.
你好啊
Sup?
我姐們在"來得快"窗口弄傷了脖子
So my homegirl here jacked up her neck in a drive-by.
其實是"得來速"窗口
Actually, it was a drive-thru.
我的兒童餐沒送玩具
My kid's meal didn't come with a toy
我就說了句"該死..."
and I was all "hell no--"
-能讓醫生看看嗎  -當然
- Could I see the doctor? - Sure.
-他馬上就來  -好的
- He'll be with you in a moment. - OK.
-裝成很痛的樣子  -什么
- Act like you're in pain. - What?
我們先檢查一下你的生命體征
Okay, we'll start by checking your vitals.
你既是收銀員又是醫生
Wow, you're a cashier and a doctor.
-二面手啊  -我還是名公證員
- You're a double threat. - I'm also a notary public,
別說我了  治療費兩百元
but enough about me. Consultation's 200 bucks
內含半盎司大麻
And it includes a half-ounce.
半盎司要兩百元
Uh, 200 for a half-sack?
簡直是明搶啊  哥們
That's a straight ripoff, g.
學齡前兒童美式英語教學片  提高兒童口語表達
別演了  《愛探險的朵拉》
Cut the act, Dora the Explorer.
要是你能找到更便宜的  請便
If you can find a better price somewhere else, hit the road.
我是能找到更便宜的
Oh, I can find a better price.
但我不想大晚上去乘公交車
But I don't like to take the bus after dark.
艾略特  喬什一個人在辦公室里
Elliot, Josh is alone in his office.
這正是向他申請加薪的好時機
It's a perfect time to ask for a raise.
我剛又加了一次薪
I just got another one.
我不能這么做
I can't do that.
要是他罵我怎么辦  我已經冒汗了
What if he yells at me? I'm already starting to sweat.
艾略特  喬什不是你的爸爸
Elliot, Josh isn't your daddy.
不管你有多少次想坐在他大腿上
No matter how many times you try to sit on his lap.
爸爸...我是說  喬什
Hey, dad-- I mean, Josh?
我有事想跟你聊聊
I was wondering if I could talk to you about something.
好吧
Okay, look,
我知道加比跟庫珀打電話的時候
I know when Gabi was talking to Cooper,
我情緒有些不穩
I let my feelings bubble up a little bit,
但這情況不會再出現了
but it's not gonna happen again.
我得專注于當她的老板這一身份
I've just got to focus on being her boss
并且當好它
and being professional.
說得太好了  喬什
That's brilliant, Josh.
要是我手里有杯酒
If I had a glass,
我會為你而舉杯
I would raise it to you.
舉起來[加薪]
Raise.
這真是個有趣的詞  對吧
That's a funny word, huh?
你沒事吧  艾略特
Everything okay, Elliot?
我在你手下工作也有一陣子了
See, I've worked for you for a while,
這地方對我而言就如同家一般
and this place is like a home to me,
美國有線新聞網的王牌新聞主播  已出柜
除了沒有安德森·庫珀的神龕
except there's no shrine to Anderson Cooper.
你生病了嗎
Are you sick?
你出了很多汗
You're sweating, like, a lot.
是嗎
Am I?
-你沒事吧  -再好不過了
- Are you okay? - Never better.
聊得很愉快  先走一步
Good talk. Gotta go.
妹子  你在用大麻烹飪嗎
Girl, are you cooking with weed?
你怎么回事啊
What is wrong with you?
別緊張  尤蘭達  經過喬什允許了
It's cool, Yolanda. Josh is letting me.
那快給我一杯果汁金酒
Then fix me up a gin and juice
讓我們在這頂樓嗨翻天
and let's blow this penthouse party up!
我做這菜是為了我的文章
I'm making edibles for my article
而且我得在三點前交稿
and I have to turn these in by 3:00.
-你們好  -喬什
- Hey, guys. - Oh, hey, Josh.
謝謝你讓我用廚房
Thank you so much for letting me use the kitchen.
-你是我的英雄  -不
- You're my hero. - No.
我只是一個
Just your boss
完全從專業能力的角度看重你的老板
who thinks of you in a completely professional capacity only.
我知道怎么回事了
Oh, I know what's going on.
你擔心我會跳槽  離你而去
You're worried that I'm gonna get another job and leave you.
要是你想走
Ha ha, well, if you left,
我會讓你走的
I'd let you go
因為我非常善于放手
because I am very good at letting go.
你不必擔心這事
You don't have to worry about that.
我沒擔心  說說而已  我真沒這么想
I'm not. That would be a feeling and I don't have those.
再見
Bye-e-e.
他看起來壓力很大
He seems really stressed.
我這些留點給他吃
I'm gonna put a few of these aside for him.
加比  別吃太多
Gabi, don't taste too much of that.
我有個朋友嗑藥嗑多了  她跟豆袋椅做愛了
I had a friend get so high, she had sex with a beanbag chair.
別擔心  我只吃一點點
Don't worry. I'm only taking tiny tastes.
我得確保吃上去沒有大麻味
I have to make sure it doesn't taste like pot
不然洛根不會用這篇文章的
or Logan's not gonna use it in the article.
好吧
Fine.
正常性愛滿足不了你時
Don't coming running to me
別跑來找我
when normal sex doesn't feel good anymore.
引人入勝  有趣
Engaging, funny.
"大麻"這個詞里沒有w這字母
Oh, there's no "w" in "marijuana."
你的文章讓我印象深刻
But I'm impressed.
真的嗎  -別高興得太早
Really? - Don't get too excited.
-我得先嘗下你的菜  -好
- I have to try your food first. - Ok.
天了嚕  你確定這里面放大麻了
Son of a bitch. Are you sure there's marijuana in this?
放了好多呢  就像是塞斯·羅根的電影
Tons. It's like a Seth Rogan movie in there.
恭喜你  加比  你的第一篇文章通過了
Congrats, Gabi. You got your first article.
天吶  太感謝你了
Oh my God, thank you so much.
洛根  抱歉打擾
Logan, I'm sorry to interrupt.
什么事  我正在會見一名天才新寫手
What? I'm meeting with a very talented new writer.
我們有麻煩了
We've got a problem.
特麗莎剛剛簽約了新的廚藝節目
Trisha just got offered her own cooking show
不在這干了
and quit.
-不是吧[出去]  -不  這是真的
- Get out. - No, it's true.
我是對你說的  出去
No, I'm talking to you. Get out.
那個梨形身材的賤人兼職就賺了六位數的薪水
That pear-shaped bitch was making six figures working part time.
這么短的時間里我要去哪
Where the hell am I gonna find another food editor
再找一名美食編輯
on such short notice?
你說的是六位數還是簡筆畫
Did you say six figures or stick figures?
有個瘋狂的主意
Crazy idea.
加比  你對擔任我們的
Gabi, you wouldn't have any interest
美食編輯有興趣嗎
in being our food editor, would you?
-真的嗎  -當然
- Seriously? - Absolutely.
我覺得你是當今美食的代言人
I think you're the modern voice of food today.
而且比那個母牛特麗莎漂亮多了
And so much prettier than that cow Trisha.
天吶  洛根  謝謝你
Oh my God, Logan, thank you so much.
這是我夢寐以求的工作
This would be my dream job.
我同意
The answer is yes!
一千一萬個同意
Yes, yes, yes,
加比
Gabi.
醒醒
Wake up.
喬什
Josh?
我覺得那你試吃太多你做的菜
I think you sampled too many of your recipes.
不省人事了
You passed out hard.
我不是《舊金山月刊》的美食編輯嗎
I'm not the food editor of San Francisco Monthly?
不是
No.
我的親娘啊
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
天了嚕  我三點就該把這些東西送去的
Oh my God, oh my God, I have to get these in by 3:00
現在外面天都已經黑了
and it's totally dark outside.
告訴我那是日食
Tell me there's a solar eclipse!
-現在是晚上九點  -不
- It's 9:00 pm. - No!
我錯過了截止時間就因為我嗑多了
I missed my deadline 'cause I was stoned!
大麻該被禁才對
This stuff should be illegal.
猜猜看誰又當回了23歲的失敗者
Guess who's back to being a 23-year-old loser?
高管培訓手冊
不是我  那肯定就是你了
Well, not me, so it must be you.
這話真刻薄
Hey, that's mean.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
成功改變了我
Success has changed me.
快  告訴我發生了什么
Come on, tell me everything.
我被我自己做的菜嗨暈了
Well, I got stoned off my own food,
在一堆臟衣服上睡著了  還錯過了截止時間
fell asleep in a pile of laundry and missed my deadline
現在洛根根本不肯見我
now Logan won't even see me!
如果說我還有什么拿手的  那一定是失敗
At least I'm a success at failing.
瞧瞧你  失敗了還這么樂觀
Look at you finding the silver lining.
積極向上  正是斯度納先生書里的第五章
Positive attitude. That's Chapter V of Mr. Stubner's book.
我還重看了他的TED演講
I am also rewatching his TED talk
關注了他家狗的推特
and following his dog on twitter.
明天的面試我一定能成功
I am gonna nail this interview tomorrow.
我不想再見到這些
I don't even want to see these anymore.
別啊  我們花了不少錢在里面呢
Whoa, no, we put a lot of money into these.
第八章  絕不浪費庫存
Chapter VIII-- never waste inventory.
我來嘗嘗味道怎么樣
Let me see if these are any good.
等等  這玩意勁很大的
Wait. Hold on. They're really strong.
得了吧  妹子
Bitch, please.
你覺得小索這點大麻都受不了嗎
You think lil so-so's afraid of a little chronic?
天吶  加比  真好吃
Oh my god. Gabi, these are delicious.
我想到了一個超棒的主意
I just had a great idea.
天吶  這些太好吃了
Oh my god, these are amazing.
要不是我已經抽嗨了  我真想再吃幾個
They make me wish I wasn't already stoned.
沒錯  就是這么贊
Yeah, they're that good.
而且它們很小
And they're small,
這樣你抽嗨了以后再想吃東西也不會撐著
so you won't be full when you get the munchies.
你怎么說
So what do you think?
我出5塊錢一個
I'll give you five bucks a piece.
-10塊  -8塊再加個海豚煙筒
- 10. - Eight and I'll throw in a dolphin bong.
9塊  加兩個蒸餾器
Nine. Make it two vaporizers
再幫我把護照公證了
and I'm gonna need a copy of my passport notarized.
你真會講價  成交
You drive a hard bargain, but deal.
下周給我100個可以嗎
Can you get me 100 by next week?
100個
A hundred?
9塊一個
At $9 a piece.
那可是9000塊啊
That's $9,000.
沒錯  是的
Yes. Yes, it is.
-羅德里格斯小姐  -斯度納先生
- Miss Rodriguez? - Mr. Stubner.
你怎么會在這
What are you doing here?
我怎么會在這  天吶
What am I doing here? Oh my god.
我不是來這給盲人讀書的
This is not where I read to the blind.
索菲亞  我們都知道我的工作壓力很大
Sofia, we both know my job is stressful.
你以為我這么頻繁去洗手間是為什么
What do you think I do during all those bathroom breaks?
我以為你有腸易激綜合癥
I thought you had I.B.S.
要來點迷你乳蛋餅嗎  斯度納先生
Mini quiche, Mr. Stubner?
那我就不客氣了
Oh, oh, don't mind if I do.
順便說句  你剛才談判很厲害
Very impressive negotiation, by the way.
真的嗎  謝謝
Really? Thank you.
你果斷直接  毫不遲疑
You were direct and no nonsense.
公司里需要的就是這種人
We admire that at the firm.
知道嗎
You know what?
你不需要面試  升職機會是你的了
You don't need to interview. The promotion is yours.
天吶  太感謝了
Oh my god. Thank you!
謝謝  謝謝  謝謝
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
索菲亞  醒醒
Sofia. Sofia, wake up!
我不會讓你失望的  斯度納先生
I won't let you down, Mr. Stubner.
什么  快醒醒  你睡著了
What? Wake up. You fell asleep.
什么  真的嗎
What? I did?
這么說我不是斯度納先生的新任初級副總裁嗎
So I'm not Mr. Stubner's new junior vice president?
不是
No.
幾點了
What time is it?
早上10點
10:00 am.
老天  我睡過了面試的時間
Oh my god, I slept through my interview!
你為什么不叫醒我
Why didn't you wake me up?
我最不負責任了  你知道的
I'm irresponsible! It's kind of my thing!
斯度納先生的書里有一整章講的都是
Mr. Stubner has an entire chapter in his book
守時的重要性
about the importance of being punctual.
他一定不會再給我升職了
He'll never promote me now.
老天  這下我又變回23歲的廢柴了
God. I'm a 23-year-old loser again.
這樣的話  歡迎回來
Well, welcome back.
塑料刀叉和偷來的番茄醬包
The plastic silverware and stolen ketchup packets
都很想念你呢
have missed you.
至少我們還有工作
Well, at least we still have jobs.
是啊
Yeah.
除非我們因為遲到被炒了  快走
Unless we get fired for being totally late! Come on!
我做到了
I did it!
我終于想到了一個好辦法要求加薪
I finally came up with a way to ask for a raise.
我用手機錄了一段
I made a recording on my phone
自己沉著自信地要求加薪的錄音
of me asking for one in a calm confident voice.
然后去見喬什的時候對嘴型就好了
That I'm going to lip sync to when I meet with Josh.
你是被領結勒得大腦缺氧了嗎
Is your bow tie on too tight?
你就看著吧
You just watch.
喬什  是我
Josh, it's me...
艾略特  這么多年來
Elliot, your hardworking,
一直勤勤懇懇  兢兢業業
competent and favorite employee.
你最喜歡的員工
of many years.
毛球  別鬧
Fluffykins, no!
我會處理掉的
I'll edit that out.
總而言之
So in summation,
我希望你能給我提升一點待遇
I would really appreciate an increase in salary,
也就是大家常說的加薪
more commonly known as a raise.
你覺得怎么樣
So what do you think?
這是我看過最爛的功夫片了
That was the worst kung fu movie I've ever seen.
-午餐好了嗎  -當然了
- Hey, is lunch ready? - Sure is!
這是什么
What's all this?
是我為你準備的特別午餐
It's a special lunch that I made for you.
不是每個老板都會允許他的員工
Not a lot of bosses will let their employees
在洗衣房地上睡上五小時的
take a five-hour nap on the laundry room floor.
是啊  也沒多少員工會這樣
Yup. Not a lot of employees would do that.
我能問你個問題嗎
Listen, can I ask you something?
-私人問題嗎  -不  完全是工作上的
- Is it personal? - No, it's completely work-related.
-那盡管問  -好吧
- Ask away. - Okay.
你有沒有試過
So have you ever been so close
最渴望的東西在你面前唾手可得
to getting something that you really wanted
到頭來卻又失之交臂
and then it just slipped through your fingers?
我的意思是
What I'm asking is
你都是怎么面對失敗的
how do you deal with failure?
這個嘛  首先
Well, first of all,
-失敗很不爽  -可不是嗎
- it sucks. - Right?
你會感覺糟透了
Yeah, you feel horrible.
試著不再去想
You try to stop thinking about it,
卻總忍不住在腦海中反復重演那一幕
but you keep playing it over in your head over and over,
然后你的朋友會開始可憐你
and then your friends start pitying you,
你怎么辦  只能告訴他們你已經看開了
so what do you do? You have to tell them you've moved on.
但你怎么真正放下呢
But how do you get past it?
我也不知道  假裝你沒事就好
I don't know. Just pretend you're fine.
或許這樣能給你足夠的時間想明白
It buys you time until hopefully you realize that...
任何事情發生都是有原因的
everything happens for a reason
或許有時候失敗
and maybe things didn't work out
是因為有更好的事在等著你
because there's something better out there for you.
比用大麻烹飪更好的事
Something better than cooking with drugs?
我想你說得對
I think you're right.
-謝謝你  喬什  你真是個好朋友  -老板
- Thanks, Josh. You're a really good friend. - Boss.
-好友老板  -老板好友
- Friend-boss. - Boss-friend.
好吧
Okay.
你是有什么要緊事要跟我說
So what's this important thing you needed to talk to me about?
喬什
Josh.
我可不可以
May I...
要求
have a...
加薪
...raise?
這就是你為什么總怪怪的嗎
Is this why you've been acting so weird?
是的
好吧  你想加多少
Okay, so how much were you thinking?
跟尤蘭達一樣
What Yolanda makes.
再多一塊錢
Plus one dollar.
行  艾略特  沒問題
Okay, Elliot, sure.
好棒
Yay!
看  其實沒有這么難吧
See? That wasn't difficult, was it?
我想讓你知道  你可以跟我說任何事
I want you to know you can come to me for anything.
-謝謝你  喬什  -不客氣
- Thanks, Josh. - You're welcome.
既然這是你第一次要求加薪
Since this was your first time asking for a raise,
還有什么別的要求嗎
anything else I can do for you?
我也不知道  不然你把衣服脫了如何
I don't know. How about you take your shirt off?
-艾略特  -抱歉
- Elliot. - Sorry.
知道嗎
You know what?
你付出了這么多
After all you've done,
脫就脫吧
I'll do it.
再脫  再脫
More, more, more!
-艾略特  醒醒  你睡著了  -什么
- Elliot, wake up. You fell asleep! - What?
這么說喬什沒有給我跳脫衣舞
So Josh didn't take his clothes off and dance for me?
沒有
No.
你的工資還是比我高
And you still make more money than me?
沒錯
Yeah.